yamatoamerica.com 2019-02-23

# Privacy Policy | Yamato Transport U.S.A.

## Privacy Policy

Yamato Transport U.S.A., Inc. (hereinafter “Yamato”) endeavors to protect the privacy of users of its website. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and in full before registering, placing an order or otherwise using the website at [yamatoamerica.com](https://yamatoamerica.com/).

### ARTICLE 1. DEFINITIONS

In this Privacy Policy, the following definitions apply:

**Applicable Privacy Law** | Applicable state and federal privacy laws, including the General Data Protection Regulation.   
---|---  
**Agreement:** | The agreement between a customer and Yamato concerning the purchase and delivery of products or services.  
**Personal Data:** | Personal data concerns any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person that is processed by Yamato.  
**Privacy Policy:** | The present Privacy Policy.  
**Processing:** | An operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.  
**Website:** | [yamatoamerica.com](https://yamatoamerica.com/)  
  
### ARTICLE 2. SCOPE OF PRIVACY POLICY

**2.1** | This Privacy Policy applies to every use of the Website by you and governs the Processing of Personal Data obtained by us via the Website.  
---|---  
**2.2** | The Website may include references of third parties (for example hyperlinks, banners or buttons). We do not control these references and are not responsible for compliance with the Applicable Privacy Law and regulations by these third parties. We recommend that you carefully read the privacy policies of the third-party websites you are visiting.   
  
### ARTICLE 3. PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED

**3.1** | 

We may collect the following Personal Data from you;

  1. name and address details;
  2. information about an order or services, including the location of a package, photocopy of passport/visa of the sender, the address details of the sender and consignee (and employee thereof);
  3. e-mail address;
  4. phone number;
  5. username and password;
  6. payment details;
  7. employment information, resume.

---|---  
**3.2** | Our Website does not collect sensitive personal data such as health data.  
**3.3** | 

Personal Data is collected by us:

  1. by registering on the Website,
  2. by placing an order;
  3. when applying for a job via the Website; or
  4. otherwise using the Website.

**3.4** | We will only process the Personal Data in accordance with Applicable Privacy Law as described in this Privacy Policy.  
  
### ARTICLE 4. PURPOSES AND LEGAL GROUND FOR PROCESSING

**4.1** | 

We collect and process your Personal Data solely for the purposes specified below:

  1. **Performance of a contract** or in order to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract: If you decide to place an order via the Website, your Personal Data may be processed by us for the Performance of the Agreement. This includes the shipments, track and trace service and handling of the payment for services. We do not process more Personal Data than is strictly necessary for the performance of the Agreement.
  2. **Communication:** Your Personal Data may be used to communicate with you about our products and services and to inform you of matters that are important for your account and/or use of the Website and the handling of any complaints. If you create an account on the Website, we will keep the Personal Data so that you do not have to enter it every time. This Processing of Personal Data is necessary for the performance of the Agreement and/or for the legitimate interest of Yamato to keep in touch with you and to offer you customer services.
  3. **Marketing purposes:** Your Personal Data may be used to send a newsletter, if you have registered for it. To approach you via e-mail for marketing purposes, we always request your prior consent, unless it concerns offers about similar products that you have ordered. You always have the right and option to unsubscribe from mailings. This Processing of Personal Data is either necessary for the legitimate interest of Yamato to keep in touch with you and to offer you similar products and services or is based on prior consent.
  4. **Customer service:** If you use customer service, your Personal Data may be used to provide you with customer service. This Processing of your Personal Data is necessary for the legitimate interest of Yamato to provide such services.
  5. **Job applications:** If you apply for a job via our website, your Personal Data may be used by us to handle your job application. This Processing of your Personal Data is necessary for the legitimate interest of Yamato to hire people.

---|---  
**4.2** | If we intend to further process the Personal Data for a purpose other than the purpose for which that Personal Data was collected, we will provide you with information about that other purpose and all relevant information before commencement of that further processing.  
  
### ARTICLE 5. TRANSFER OF PERSONAL DATA TO THIRD PARTIES

**5.1** | We share your Personal Data within the Yamato Group.  
If and insofar as we transfer Personal Data with parties in countries that do not have an adequate level of protection, we will agree to use Standard Contractual Clauses with these parties to ensure an adequate level of protection of your personal data.  
---|---  
  
### ARTICLE 6. SECURITY

**6.1** | We take appropriate organizational and technical security measures to protect your Personal Data and to prevent misuse, loss or alteration thereof. In addition, we limit access to Personal Data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a need for access. Also, the aforementioned persons involved are bound by a confidentiality obligation, either in their employment agreements or (data processor) contracts.  
---|---  
**6.2** | We have internal safety guidelines in place including a data breach policy which describes how to deal with a suspected Personal Data breach. We will notify the relevant supervisory authority and the data subjects involved if required under Applicable Privacy Law.  
  
### ARTICLE 7. RETENTION PERIODS

**7.1** | We do not store your Personal Data any longer than strictly necessary for the purposes for which we collect the Personal Data.  
---|---  
**7.2** | If you are in European Economic Area (“EEA”), you may request Yamato to delete the Personal Data at any stage. If the Personal Data is no longer required for the purposes for which we collected or otherwise Processed the Personal Data, we will remove the Personal Data.  
  
### ARTICLE 8. COOKIES

**8.1** | We use cookies to ensure that the Website functions properly.  
---|---  
**8.2** | 

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by the browser on your computer. Yamato uses different types of cookies for different purposes.

  1. Functional cookies: cookies that are necessary for the Website to function properly, including cookies that are necessary to create an account;
  2. Analytical cookies: cookies that ensure that insight can be gained into how you use (parts of) the Website, so that Yamato can improve the Website and that it fits as well as possible with what you find interesting and important. Yamato does not use the data obtained with these cookies to study the use of the Website at an individual level, but only at an aggregated level.

**8.3** | We only use third party cookies to improve the quality and effectiveness of the Website. For example, it uses Google Analytics, which is set up in a privacy-friendly manner.  
**8.4** | Most browsers are set to accept cookies by default. You can set the browser to disable cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, it is possible that some functions and services of both Yamato and other websites may not function properly if cookies are disabled.  
  
### ARTICLE 9. YOUR RIGHTS

**9.1** | You have the right to withdraw consent at any time, where relevant and when permissible under Applicable Privacy Law  
---|---  
**9.2** | You have the right to request access to your Personal Data, where relevant and when permissible under Applicable Privacy Law. This enables you to receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you.  
**9.3** | You have the right to request correction of the Personal Data that we hold about you, where relevant and when permissible under Applicable Privacy Law. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected.  
**9.4** | You have the right to request deletion of your Personal Data, where relevant and when permissible under Applicable Privacy Law. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove Personal Data where there is no good reason for us continuing to Process it.  
**9.5** | You have the right to object to Processing of your Personal Data where we are relying on a legitimate interest, where relevant and when permissible under Applicable Privacy Law. Insofar as the Processing of your Personal Data takes place for direct marketing purposes, we will always honour your request. For Processing for other purposes, we will also cease and desist Processing, unless we have compelling legitimate grounds for the Processing which override your interests, rights and freedoms or that are related to the institution, exercise or substantiation of a legal claim.  
**9.6** | You have the right to request restriction of Processing of your Personal Data, where relevant and when permissible under Applicable Privacy Law.  
**9.7** | You have the right to request the transfer of your Personal Data to you or to a third party, where relevant and when permissible under Applicable Privacy Law. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your Personal Data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.  
**9.8** | The exercise of the abovementioned rights, where relevant and when permissible under Applicable Privacy Law, is free of charge. We will provide you with information about the follow-up to the request immediately and in any case within one month of receipt of the request. Depending on the complexity of the request and on the number of requests, this period can be extended by another two months. We will notify you of such an extension within one month of receipt of the request.  
**9.9** | If your requests are manifestly unfounded or excessive, in particular because of the repetitive character, we will either charge you a reasonable fee or refuse to comply with the request.  
**9.10** | In addition to the above-mentioned rights you have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority at all times. However, we would appreciate the chance to deal with your concerns before you approach the supervisory authority so please contact us beforehand.  
  
### ARTICLE 10. CONTACT DETAILS

**10.1** | 

For any questions, complaints or in the event that you wish to make use of one of the rights mentioned in Article 9 of this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at the contact details below:

| **Address:** | 1055 W. Victoria St., Compton, CA 90220  
---|---  
**Email address:** | privacy@yamatoamerica.com  
**Telephone number:** | 1 424-529-5160  
**10.2** | Yamato has also appointed a privacy officer, who can be contacted at: privacy@yamatoamerica.com.  
  
### ARTICLE 11. MISCELLANEOUS

**11.1** | Yamato is entitled at all times to delete your account without notice. In such a case, Yamato owes no compensation to the Customer as a result of the termination of the account.  
---|---  
**11.2** | Yamato reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy on a regular basis. It is your responsibility to regularly review the applicable conditions. This Privacy Policy is last amended and revised in May 2018.  
**11.3** | If a provision from this Privacy Policy is in conflict with the law, it will be replaced by a provision of the same purport that reflects the original intention of the provision, all this to the extent legally permissible. In that case, the remaining provisions remain applicable unchanged.  
**11.4** | We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register or use our services or send any Personal Information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected Personal Data from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a child under 13 may have provided us Personal Information, please contact us at privacy@yamatoamerica.com.
